Finding Aid for the Kemp Tolley/James Stahlman Collection
Special Collections Manuscripts and Rare Books
Kemp Tolley/James Stahlman Collection
1973-1986
Special Collections Manuscripts and Rare Books
MSS.0460
.07 linear_feet
Scope and Contents
This collection contains copies of correspondence between Kemp Tolley and James Stahlman. It also contains an essay, and 2 copies of newsletters edited by Kemp Tolley. The letters discuss a wide range of topics: World War II, Cuba, China, Russia, Roberts Commission, Kennedy Assassination, and the Warren Commission.
- Correspondence
  - November 21, 1973
  - November 26, 1973
  - November 30, 1973
  - April 26, 1974
  - April 29, 1974
  - March 10, 1975
  - March 24, 1975
  - April 28, 1975
  - May 7, 1975
  - June 9, 1975
  - December 22, 1975
  - February 10, 1976
  - February 18, 1976
  - March 8, 1976
  - April 13, 1976
- Essay on Incredible Hypotheses, by Preston Slosson, undated
- Magazines
  - ‘Yangtze & South China Patroller’, September 1, 1984
  - ‘China Gunboatman’ Summer, 1986